<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Smart College</string>


    <string-array name="Main">
        <item> Timetable </item>
        <item> Subjects </item>
        <item> Faculty </item>
        <item> CompSa </item>
        <item> College Curriculum </item>
        <item> Student Information </item>
        <item>  Placements </item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Description">

        <item> TE-A </item>
        <item> Includes Subjects of TE-Comp </item>
        <item> Details of Faculty </item>
        <item> CompSa Events </item>
        <item> Includes Activities of College </item>
        <item> Data of student ex.Roll no,Branch,year.. </item>
        <item> Includes placed students from DYPIEMR</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Week">
        <item> Monday </item>
        <item> Tuesday </item>
        <item> Wednesday </item>
        <item> Thursday </item>
        <item> Friday </item>
        <item> Saturday </item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Monday">
        <item> TA1-CN TA2,TA3 -DBMS TA4-SDL </item>
        <item> BREAK </item>
        <item> SEPM  </item>
        <item> DBMS  </item>
        <item> SHORT BREAK </item>
        <item> SDL TUT-KN </item>
        <item> CN SAP </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Tuesday">
        <item> TA1-SDL TA2-CN TA3-SDL TA4-DBMS</item>
        <item> BREAK </item>
        <item> CN  </item>
        <item> TOC  </item>
        <item> SHORT BREAK </item>
        <item> DBMS  </item>
        <item> SEPM  </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Wednesday">
        <item> TA1-DBMS TA2,TA3,TA4-SDL </item>
        <item> BREAK </item>
        <item> ISEE  </item>
        <item> TOC  </item>
        <item> SHORT BREAK </item>
        <item> SEPM </item>
        <item> FREE TIME </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Thursday">
        <item> TA1-SDL TA2,TA3-DBMS TA4-CN </item>
        <item> BREAK </item>
        <item> ISEE  </item>
        <item> CN  </item>
        <item> SHORT BREAK </item>
        <item> DBMS  </item>
        <item> SDL  </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Friday">
        <item> TA1-DBMS TA2-SDL TA3-CN TA4-DBMS </item>
        <item> BREAK </item>
        <item> CN  </item>
        <item> TOC  </item>
        <item> SHORT BREAK </item>
        <item> ISEE  </item>
        <item> FREE TIME </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Saturday">
        <item> Extra Lecture </item>
        <item> Guest Lecture </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="time1">
        <item>"10.10AM - 12.10PM</item>
        <item>"12.10AM - 12.50PM</item>
        <item>"12.50PM - 1.45PM</item>
        <item>"1.45PM - 2.40PM</item>
        <item>"2.40PM - 2.50PM</item>
        <item>"2.50PM - 3.45PM</item>
        <item>"3.45PM - 4.40PM</item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="time2">
        <item>"10.10AM - 12.10PM</item>
        <item>"12.10AM - 12.50PM</item>
        <item>"12.50PM - 1.45PM</item>
        <item>"1.45PM - 2.40PM</item>
        <item>"2.40PM - 2.50PM</item>
        <item>"2.50PM - 3.45PM</item>
        <item>"3.45PM - 4.40PM</item>


    </string-array>


    <string-array name="time3">
        <item>"10.10AM - 12.10PM</item>
        <item>"12.10AM - 12.50PM</item>
        <item>"12.50PM - 1.45PM</item>
        <item>"1.45PM - 2.40PM</item>
        <item>"2.40PM - 2.50PM</item>
        <item>"2.50PM - 3.45PM</item>
        <item>"3.45PM - 4.40PM</item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="time4">
        <item>"10.10AM - 12.10PM</item>
        <item>"12.10AM - 12.50PM</item>
        <item>"12.50PM - 1.45PM</item>
        <item>"1.45PM - 2.40PM</item>
        <item>"2.40PM - 2.50PM</item>
        <item>"2.50PM - 3.45PM</item>
        <item>"3.45PM - 4.40PM</item>


    </string-array>


    <string-array name="time5">
        <item>"10.10AM - 12.10PM</item>
        <item>"12.10AM - 12.50PM</item>
        <item>"12.50PM - 1.45PM</item>
        <item>"1.45PM - 2.40PM</item>
        <item>"2.40PM - 2.50PM</item>
        <item>"2.50PM - 3.45PM</item>
        <item>"3.45PM - 4.40PM</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="time6">
        <item>"10.10AM - 12.10PM"</item>
        <item>                   </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="Subjects">
        <item> Database Management System </item>
        <item> Theory Of Computation </item>
        <item> Software Engineering and Management </item>
        <item> Information Systems and Engineering Economics </item>
        <item> Computer Networks </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="DBMS">
    <item>Introduction to Database Management Systems, Purpose of Database Systems, DatabaseSystem
Applications, View of Data, Database Languages, Database System Structure, Data Models,
Database Design and ER Model Entity, Attributes, Relationships, Constraints, Keys, Design
Process, Entity Relationship Model, ER Diagram, Design Issues, Extended ER Features,
converting ER and EER diagram into tables</item>

        <item>SQL: Characteristics and advantages, SQL Data Types and Literals, DDL, DML, DCL, TCL,SQL Operators, Tables: Creating, Modifying, Deleting, Views: Creating, Dropping, Updating
using Views, Indexes, SQL DML Queries: SELECT Query and clauses, Set Operations,Predicates and Joins, Set membership, Tuple Variables, Set comparison, Ordering of Tuples,
Aggregate Functions, Nested Queries, Database Modification using SQL Insert, Update andDelete Queries. PLSQL: concept of Stored Procedures and Functions, Cursors, Triggers,
Assertions, roles and privileges , Embedded SQL, Dynamic SQL</item>

        <item>Relational Model Basic concepts, Attributes and Domains, CODDs Rules, Relational IntegrityDomain, Referential , Enterprise Constraints, Database Design Features of Good
Relational Designs, Normalization, Atomic Domains and First Normal Form,  Functional Dependencies, Algorithms for Decomposition, 2NF, 3NF, , Modeling
Temporal Data.
</item>

        <item>Basic concept of a Transaction, Transaction Management, Properties of Transactions, Concept ofSchedule, Serial Schedule,  Conflict and View, Cascaded Aborts, Recoverable and
Non-recoverable Schedules, Concurrency Control: Need, Locking Methods, Deadlocks, Methods, Recovery methods  ShadowPaging and LogBased Recovery, Checkpoints,
Query Processing, Query Optimization, Performance Tuning.
</item>

        <item>Introduction to Database Architectures DBMS Architectures, Case study OracleArchitecture. Parallel Databases: Speedup and Scale up, Architectures of Parallel Databases.
Distributed Databases: Architecture of Distributed Databases, Distributed Database Design,Distributed Data Storage, Distributed Transaction: Basics, Failure modes, Commit Protocols,
Concurrency Control in Distributed Database</item>

        <item>Introduction to NoSQL Database, Types and examples of NoSQL Database Key value store,
document store, graph, Performance, Structured verses unstructured data, Distributed Database
Model, CAP theorem and BASE Properties, Comparative study of SQL and NoSQL, NoSQL
Data Models, Case Study unstructured data from social media. Introduction to Big Data,MapReduce.
</item>


    </string-array>


    <string-array name="TOC">


 <item>Introduction to Formal language, introduction to language translation logic, Essentials of translation, Alphabets and languages, Finite representation of language, Finite Automata (FA): An
Informal Picture of FA, Finite State Machine , Language accepted by FA, Definition of Regular Language, Deterministic and Nondeterministic FA, epsilon NFA, FA
with output Moore and Mealy machines Definition, models, interconversion.Case Study FSM for vending machine, spell checker</item>

        <item>Operators of RE, Building RE, Precedence of operators, Algebraic laws for RE, Conversions: NFA to DFA, RE to DFA Conversions: RE to DFA, DFA to RE Conversions: State/loop elimination,
Arden theorem Properties of Regular Languages Pumping Lemma for Regular languages,Closure and Decision properties.Case Study: RE in text search and replace </item>

        <item>Introduction, Regular Grammar, Context Free Grammar Definition, Derivation, Language of grammar, sentential form, parse tree, inference, derivation, parse trees, ambiguity in grammar and
Language- ambiguous Grammar, Simplification of CFG Eliminating unit productions, useless production, useless symbols, and productions, Normal Forms Chomsky normal form,
Greibach normal form, Closure properties of CFL, Decision properties of CFL, ChomskyHierarchy, Application of CFG: Parser, Markup languages, XML and Document Type
Definitions.Case Study- CFG for Palindromes, Parenthesis Match, Turing Machine Model, Representation of Turing Machines, Language Acceptability by Turing
Machines, Design of TM, Description of TM, Techniques for TM Construction, Variants of TuringMachines, The Model of Linear Bounded Automata , TM and Type 0 grammars, TM Halting
Problem.</item>

        <item>Turing Machine Model, Representation of Turing Machines, Language Acceptability by TuringMachines, Design of TM, Description of TM, Techniques for TM Construction, Variants of Turing
Machines, The Model of Linear Bounded Automata , TM and Type  grammars,  HaltingProblem.
</item>

        <item>Basic Definitions, Equivalence of Acceptance by Finite State and Empty stack, PDA and Context FreeLanguage, Equivalence of PDA and CFG, Parsing and PDA: Top-Down Parsing, Topdown Parsing
Using Deterministic PDA, Bottom-up Parsing, Closure properties and Deterministic PDA.
</item>

        <item>A Language that is not recursively enumerable, An undecidable problem that is RE, Post
Correspondence Problem, The Classes P and NP  Problems Solvable in Polynomial Time, An
Example Kruskal Algorithm, Nondeterministic Polynomial Time, An NP Example The
Traveling Salesman Problem, Polynomial-Time Reductions NP Complete Problems, An NPComplete
Problem The Satisfiability Problem, Tractable and Intractable Representing SAT
Instances, NP Completeness of the SAT Problem, A Restricted Satisfiability Problem Normal
Forms for Boolean Expressions, Converting Expressions to CNF, The Problem of Independent
Sets, The NodeCover Problem.</item>


    </string-array>


    <string-array name="SEPM">

        <item>Software Engineering Fundamentals Nature of Software, Software Engineering Principles,The Software Process, Software Myths. Process Models A Generic Process Model, Prescriptive
Process Models The Waterfall, Incremental Process, Evolutionary Process, UnifiedProcess, Concurrent. Advanced Process Models and Tools: Agile software development Agile
methods and agile development, Extreme programming Practices, Testing in XP,Pair programming Introduction to agile tools
Case Studies An information system , wilderness weather system</item>

        <item>Requirements Engineering: User and system requirements, Functional and non-functional requirements, Types and Metrics, A spiral view of the requirements engineering process. Software
Requirements Specification  The software requirements Specification document, The structure of SRS, Ways of writing a SRS, structured and tabular SRS for an insulin pump case
study, Requirements elicitation and Analysis Process, Requirements validation, Requirements management. Case Studies The information system.
Case study  Mental health care patient management system </item>

        <item>Design Process and quality, Design Concepts, The design Model, Pattern based Software Design.Architectural Design :Design Decisions, Views, Patterns, Application Architectures, Modeling
Component level Design: component, Designing class based components, conducting component level design, User Interface Design The golden rules, Interface Design steps and
Analysis, Design Evaluation, Case Study Web App Interface Design</item>

        <item>Project Management Concepts The Management Spectrum, People, Product, Process, Project,The W5HH Principle, Metrics in the Process and Project Domains, Software Measurement  size
and function oriented metrics, Metrics for Project and Software Quality, Project Estimation Observations on Estimation, Project Planning Process, Software Scope and
feasibility, Resources Human Resources, Reusable software, Environmental Resources. Software Project Estimation, Decomposition Techniques, Empirical Estimation Models Structure,
 Estimation of  Projects, Specialized Estimation Case Study:Software Tools for Estimation, Project Scheduling: Basic Concepts, Defining a Task Set for the
Software Project, Defining Task Network, Scheduling with timeline charts, Schedule trackingTools:- Microsoft Project, Daily Activity Reporting and Tracking </item>


        <item>Project Risk Management  Risk Analysis and Management Reactive versus Proactive Risk Strategies, Software Risks, Risk Identification, Risk Projection, Risk Refinement, Risk Mitigation,
Risks Monitoring and Management, The  plan for case study projectSoftware Configuration Management: The SCM repository, SCM process, Configuration
management for WebApps, Case study CVS and Subversion Tools, Visual Source Safe from Microsoft and Clear Case. Maintenance and   Software Maintenance, Software
Supportability,  Business Process  Software  ReverseEngineering, Restructuring, Forward Engineering</item>

        <item>Introduction to Software Testing, Principles of Testing, Testing Life Cycle, Phases of Testing,
Types of Testing, Verification and Validation, Defect Management, Defect Life Cycle, Bug
Reporting, GUI Testing, Test Management and Automation.</item>


    </string-array>


    <string-array name="ISEE">

    <item>Role of Information Systems in Organizations, The Information System Manager and his
challenges, Concepts of Information Systems, Information Systems and Management Strategy
Case Studies  Information Systems in the Indian Railways, Information Systems in an eCommerce
Organization.
</item>

        <item>Managing Information Systems, Ethical and Social Issues, Information Technology Infrastructure
and Choices, Information Systems Security and Control,
Case Studies Information Technology Infrastructure in a Bank, Information Technology
Infrastructure in a manufacturing  process industry.</item>


        <item>Information Systems Development and Project Management, Managing Data Resources,
Business Process Integration and Enterprise Systems, ICT for Development and EGovernance,
Case Studies   or cloud based ERP implementation,  Unique Identification
Authority of India</item>


        <item>Engineering Economic Decisions, Time Value of Money, Understanding Money Management,
Case Studies Economic decisions done in Multinational companies</item>

        <item>Equivalence Calculations under Inflation, Present-Worth Analysis, AnnualEquivalence Analysis.
Case Studies comparative analysis of software enterprises from similar domains.</item>

        <item>Accounting for Depreciation and Income Taxes, Project CashFlow Analysis, Understanding
Financial Statements, Case Studies  cash flow analysis done in startup companies.</item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="CN">
        <item>Introduction of LAN MAN WAN PAN,  Network, Network Architectures Client Server;
Peer To Peer Distributed and SDN, OSI Model, TCP IP Model, Topologies Star and
Hierarchical Design issues for Layers, Transmission Mediums CAT5, 5e, 6, OFC and Radio
Spectrum, Network Devices Bridge, Switch, Router, and Access Point, Manchester and
Differential Manchester Encodings 802.11 Frequency Hopping  and Direct
Sequence
</item>

        <item>Design Issues: Services to Network Layer, Framing, Error Control and Flow Control. Error
Control: Parity Bits, Hamming Codes  and CRC. Flow Control Protocols Unrestricted
Simplex, Stop and Wait, Sliding Window Protocol, WAN Connectivity  PPP and </item>


        <item>Channel allocation: Static and Dynamic, Multiple Access Protocols Pure and Slotted ALOHA,
  802.3 Standards and Frame Formats,  CD, Binary Exponential Back
off algorithm, Fast Ethernet, Gigabit Ethernet,  802.11 and  802.15 and
802.16 Standards, Frame formats</item>


        <item>Switching techniques, IP Protocol, IPv4 and IPv6 addressing schemes,  NAT,
 Routing Protocols: Distance Vector, Link State, Path Vector, Routing in Internet RIP
, BGP, Congestion control and QoS, Mobile IP, Routing in MANET
DSR</item>

        <item>Services, Berkley Sockets, Addressing, Connection establishment, Connection release, Flow
control and buffering, Multiplexing,  TCP Timer management, TCP Congestion Control,
Real Time Transport protocol Stream Control Transmission Protocol  Quality of
Service  Differentiated services, TCP and UDP for Wireless.
</item>

        <item>Domain Name System  Hyper Text Transfer Protocol  Email MIME,
POP3, FTP, TELNET, Dynamic Host Control Protocol  Simple Network
Management Protocol
</item>


    </string-array>


    <string-array name="titles">

        <item> Unit1 </item>
        <item> Unit2 </item>
        <item> Unit3 </item>
        <item> Unit4 </item>
        <item> Unit5 </item>
        <item> Unit6 </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="faculty_name">
        <item> Prof.Mrs.Shevatekar </item>
        <item> Mrs.Survana Patil </item>
        <item> Mrs. Ketaki Bhoyar</item>
        <item> Mr.Vishal Patil </item>
        <item> Mrs. Pooja Mishra </item>
        <item> Mrs. Rashmi Deshpande </item>
        <item> Mrs. Nalani Yadav</item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="Shevatekar">

        <item>  (+91)9922996401 </item>
        <item> pshevatekar@gmail.com</item>
        <item> Computer Department, First Floor </item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="SurvanaPatil">

        <item>  (+91)9881224977 </item>
        <item> survanaatil@gmail.com</item>
        <item> Android Lab1 </item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="KetakiBhoyar">

        <item>  (+91)8446939412 </item>
        <item> Ketakibhoyar@gmail.com</item>
        <item> Android Lab2 </item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="VishalPatil">

        <item>  (+91)7058857891  </item>
        <item> VishalPatil@gmil.com</item>
        <item> Android Lab3 </item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="PoojaMishra">

        <item>  (+91)9921257325 </item>
        <item> poojamishra@gmail.cm</item>
        <item> Android Lab4 </item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="RashmiDeshpande">

        <item> (+91)9422325572 </item>
        <item> rashmideshpande@gmail.com</item>
        <item> Android Lab5 </item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="NalaniYadav">
        <item> (+91)9881718186 </item>
        <item> nalaniyadav@gmail.com</item>
        <item> Android Lab5 </item>


    </string-array>

</resources>
